(Bernadette:)But it's weird... Howie's the one
who's been talking about
(Bernadette:)having kids for years, and I was
(Bernadette:)all excited to tell him because
I thought he'd be thrilled,
(Bernadette:)but then he started to flip out
(Bernadette:)and now this
feels like a bad idea
(Bernadette:)and I'm gonna get fat.
(Penny:)No, no, come on. Come on,
you're not gonna get fat.
(Penny:)You're gonna be beautiful
and glowing
and-and have the cutest
little baby bump ever.
(Bernadette:)Easy for you to say,
skinny bitch.
(Bernadette:)Sorry, hormones.
(Penny:)Oh, that's all right.
All I heard was "skinny."
(Amy:)I wouldn't make too much
out of Howard
(Amy:)not reacting the way
you expected him to.
(Penny:)Yeah, I'm sure
(Penny:)it was just
the initial shock of it all.
(Bernadette:)You're probably right.
(Bernadette:)After we talked about it,
he started to calm down.
(Howard:)I shouldn't be raising a kid.
(Howard:)I don't even
eat my own vegetables.
Buddy, I-I think
you might be overreacting.
(Howard:)And then there's
this nose.
(Howard:)I mean, what if he
looks like me?
(Howard:)Or worse...
what if she looks like me?
(Sheldon:)Not to mention
(Sheldon:)the impact on our social circle.